<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Clouddot Platform Blog</title>
    <link>https://redhatinsights.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Clouddot Platform Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 08:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://redhatinsights.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Delivery and Feature Flags</title>
      <link>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/continuous-delivery-and-feature-flags/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/continuous-delivery-and-feature-flags/</guid>
      <description>Our current branching model includes two branches &amp;ndash; master and stable. This allows changes not ready for production to sit on master while hotfixes can be cherry picked onto stable. While this is intuitive to understand as a developer, it is more complex when implemented in a deploy pipeline. Two sets of build artifacts are needed at any given moment, and there is always an extra cherry-pick step required to get anything to produciton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevProd team update for week of April 7</title>
      <link>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/devprod-update-2021-04-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 15:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/devprod-update-2021-04-07/</guid>
      <description>Clowder Job Support Clowder now supports Jobs! The usage doc can be found as part of the Clowder docs .
There are still features in flight for full support of IQE Jobs, but most other usecases should be covered. The DevProd team is working to close the IQE gaps, so stay tuned in the coming weeks. Feedback is always welcome and appreciated.
Managed Kafka Support The initial work to enable Managed Kafka support is underway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevProd Team - Core Vision: Clowder</title>
      <link>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/devprod-vision-2021-02-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/devprod-vision-2021-02-06/</guid>
      <description>This is the first in a series of posts that will explain the strategic goals of the Clouddot DevProd team, their key responsiblities, and how those responsibilities fit into their strategic goals. This post will focus on the rationale behind the creation of Clowder.
Strategic Goals The DevProd team&amp;rsquo;s chief concern is to improve developer productivity by focusing on two strategic goals:
 Experience: Improving developers&#39; experience of operating inside a kubernetes-based platform such as Clouddot, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevProd team update for week of February 8</title>
      <link>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/devprod-update-2021-02-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/devprod-update-2021-02-09/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy week in the land of documentation. Clowder also received some new updates paving the way for full Cyndi support, along with some important technical debt cleanup. Read all the latest updates here.
Clowder Production Updates Shared DB support has now landed in production, along with support for the private ports , which adds Clowder support for internal endpoints that are intended to be accessed via Turnpike on internal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevProd team update for week of February 1</title>
      <link>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/devprod-update-2021-02-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 15:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/devprod-update-2021-02-02/</guid>
      <description>The DevProd team is launching a blog with weekly updates on migrating apps to Clowder and ephemeral environments! This will include brief descriptions of changes and new features added to both Clowder and Bonfire, progress updates regarding specific app migrations, issues and warnings to be pertinent to dev teams, and other developments going on in the DevProd team.
Clowder Feature flags Clowder now supports passing connection information for an Unleash feature flag server in cdappconfig.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
