<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Clouddot Platform Blog</title>
    <link>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Clouddot Platform Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Developer Productivity Team - Core Vision</title>
      <link>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/devprod-vision-2021-02-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/devprod-vision-2021-02-06/</guid>
      <description>It’s important in a large ecosystem such as the Clouddot platform to understand all the moving parts, the teams involved, and their functions and driving forces. This can often help alleviate stresses and tensions by providing the context to teams decisions, ultimately revealing their core motiviations. In this blog post, the intention is to furnish the reader with an overview of the pillars that the Developer Productivity (DevProd) team is built on and how some of the projects they maintain and operate fit into the broader Clouddot ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevProd team update for week of February 8</title>
      <link>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/devprod-update-2021-02-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 15:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/devprod-update-2021-02-09/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy week in the land of documentation. Clowder also received some new updates paving the way for full Cyndi support, along with some important technical debt cleanup. Read all the latest updates here.
Clowder Production Updates Shared DB support has now landed in production, along with support for the private ports , which adds Clowder support for internal endpoints that are intended to be accessed via Turnpike on internal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevProd team update for week of February 1</title>
      <link>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/devprod-update-2021-02-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 15:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redhatinsights.github.io/blog/devprod-update-2021-02-02/</guid>
      <description>The DevProd team is launching a blog with weekly updates on migrating apps to Clowder and ephemeral environments! This will include brief descriptions of changes and new features added to both Clowder and Bonfire, progress updates regarding specific app migrations, issues and warnings to be pertinent to dev teams, and other developments going on in the DevProd team.
Clowder Feature flags Clowder now supports passing connection information for an Unleash feature flag server in cdappconfig.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
